Guide to the Peter Palmquist Collection of Women in Photography
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographic Materials, 1971-2003; Series II; (222 boxes)
  - Photographic Materials, (117 boxes)
    - Hitchcock, Jenette, Mrs. (born 1838), 6 photographic prints (Box 261, Folder 906)
      Also known as Mrs. John Hitchcock
    - Hjelm, Fanny (born 1855), 2 photographic prints (Box 261, Folder 907)
    - Hoaas, Hilda, 1 photographic print (Box 261, Folder 908)
    - Hofgreen, Selma, 1 photographic print (Box 261, Folder 909)
    - Hogan, J. J., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 261, Folder 910)
    - Hohenshelt, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 261, Folder 911)
    - Holden, F. A., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 261, Folder 912)
    - Holder, Beverly L., 1 color photographic print (Box 261, Folder 913)
    - Hollopeter, C. A., Mrs., 2 tintypes (Box 261, Folder 914)
    - Holmes, Elizabeth J. (born 1950), 2 color 35mm slides (Box 261, Folder 915)
    - Holmes, Judy, 1 serial (Box 261, Folder 916)
    - Holst, Eva, 1 photographic print (Box 261, Folder 917)
    - Holt, 1 color photographic print (Box 261, Folder 918)
    - Honn, Bessie, 3 photographic prints (Box 261, Folder 919)
    - Hooper, Grace (1899-1979), 7 serials (Box 263, Folder 920)
    - Hopkins, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 264, Folder 921)
    - Horn, Grace Chandler (1879-1967), 274 photographic prints (Box 265, Folder 922-939)
      Also known as Grace Chandler or Grace DePue
    - Horton, Nancy G. (born 1962), 1 photographic print and 1 color photographic print (Box 264, Folder 940)
    - Houseknecht, Leona, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 264, Folder 941)
    - Houser, E. F., Mrs., 9 photographic prints (Box 264, Folder 942)
    - Howe, E. W., Mrs., 1 piece of ephemera (Box 264, Folder 943)
    - Howe, M. E., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 264, Folder 944)
      Also known as Mrs. M. F. Howe
    - Hoyt, Fannie, Mrs. (born circa 1852), 6 photographic prints (Box 264, Folder 945)
    - Hubley, Grace, Miss, 16 photographic prints, 13 color photographic prints, and 2 pieces of ephemera (Box 264, Folder 946)
      Also known as Grace Hubley Jones
    - Hudson, Grace Carpenter (1865-1937), 42 photographic prints (Box 264, Folder 947)
      Also known as Grace Hudson
    - Huff Sisters, 1 photographic print (Box 264, Folder 948)
    - Huff, Emma, 1 photographic print (Box 264, Folder 949)
    - Huffman, Chastina M., Mrs., 3 photographic prints (Box 264, Folder 950)
      Also known as Huffman & Lady, P. C. Huffman, C. M. Huffman, or Lady Huffman
    - Huggins Sisters, 1 photographic print (Box 264, Folder 951)
    - Hultquist, Sigrid, 1 photographic print (Box 264, Folder 952)
    - Hunt, Marilyn (born 1957), 1 color inkjet print (Box 264, Folder 953)
    - Hurley, Mrs., 1 photographic print, hand-colored (Box 264, Folder 954)
    - Hussey, Lea R., 1 photographic print (Box 264, Folder 955)
    - Hutchinson, Bert, Mrs., 1 album (17 photographic prints) (Box 264, Folder 956)
    - Hutchinson, G. F., Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 264, Folder 957)
    - Hyde, Jettora Watkins, 11 photographic prints (Box 264, Folder 958)
    - Imershein, Betsy (born 1953), 1 black and white 35mm slide (Box 264, Folder 959)
    - Ingeberg, H, 1 photographic print (Box 264, Folder 960)
    - Ingelse, Corine, 1 photographic print (Box 264, Folder 961)
    - Irvine, Edith (1886-1949), 3 photographic prints (Box 264, Folder 962)
    - Itano, Terry, 4 color photographic prints (Box 264, Folder 963)
    - Iturbide, Graciela (born 1942), 1 photographic print (Box 264, Folder 964)
    - Jackson, Diane, 8 color 35mm slides (Box 264, Folder 965)
    - Jackson, Thelma Jessie (1915-1998), 2 color photographic prints (Box 264, Folder 966)
    - Jacobsen, Anna, 2 photographic prints (Box 264, Folder 967)
    - Jacobsen, Carol (born 1941), 36 color 35mm slides (Box 264, Folder 968)
    - Jacobson-Wenzel, Dorothea (born 1940), 3 photographic prints, and 36 color photographic prints, and 1 serial (Box 266, Folder 969)
    - Jacobsson, Selma, 2 photographic prints (Box 266, Folder 970)
    - Jaffe, Ellen, 1 black and white 35mm slide (Box 266, Folder 971)
    - Jahn, Meyer, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 266, Folder 972)
    - James, A., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 266, Folder 973)
    - James, Amy, Mrs., 3 photographic prints (Box 266, Folder 974)
    - Janson, Marina, 1 photographic print (Box 266, Folder 975)
    - Javadiangilani, Shoka (born 1978), 3 color 35mm slides (Box 266, Folder 976)
    - Jeanne, Camille, 1 photographic print (Box 266, Folder 977)
    - Jeanson, Louise, 1 photographic print (Box 266, Folder 978)
    - Jenik, Rosa, Mrs., 4 photographic prints (Box 266, Folder 979)
    - Jenkins, Amy, 1 serial (Box 266, Folder 980)
    - Jenkins, O. A., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 266, Folder 981)
    - Jenner, Michael Carolyn, 2 photographic prints and 4 color inkjet prints (Box 266, Folder 982)
    - Jensen, Alma, 2 photographic prints (Box 266, Folder 983)
    - Jensen, Hilda, 3 photographic prints (Box 266, Folder 984)
    - Jensen, Johanne, 1 photographic print (Box 266, Folder 985)
    - Jensen, Kirstine, 1 photographic print (Box 266, Folder 986)
    - Jewett, Elizabeth Caroline, Mrs. (circa 1836-1920), 5 photographic prints (Box 266, Folder 987)
      Also known as E. C. Jewett or F. H. Jewett
    - Jocelyn, Frances, Viscountess (1820-1880), 2 color photographic prints (Box 266, Folder 988)
      Also known as Lady Fanny Jocelyn
    - Johanson, Emilia, 10 photographic prints (Box 266, Folder 989)
      Also known as Emilia Johansson
    - Johanson, Hilma, 2 photographic prints (Box 266, Folder 990)
      Also known as Hilma Johansson
    - Johansson, Amanda, 2 photographic prints (Box 266, Folder 991)
    - Johansson, Anna, 2 photographic prints (Box 266, Folder 992)
    - Johansson, Ellen, 1 photographic print (Box 266, Folder 993)
    - Johnson, Adelaide, 3 photographic prints (Box 266, Folder 994)
    - Johnson, Anna, 3 photographic prints (Box 266, Folder 995)
    - Johnson, Belle (1864-1945), 5 photographic prints (Box 266, Folder 996)
      Also known as Belle Johnston
    - Johnson, Mary L., Mrs., 3 photographic prints (Box 266, Folder 997)
    - Johnson, Ruby, 1 photographic print (Box 266, Folder 998)
    - Johnston, Bryant, 4 color 35mm slides (Box 266, Folder 999)
    - Johnston, Frances Benjamin, Miss (1864-1952), 1 photographic print and 1 catalog (Box 266, Folder 1000)
      Also known as Frances B. England
    - Jones, Charles, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 266, Folder 1001)
    - Jones, D. W., Mrs. (born circa 1828), 1 photographic print (Box 266, Folder 1002)
    - Jones, Helen Lukens, Miss (born 1872), 4 photographic prints (Box 266, Folder 1003)
      Also known as Helen Lukens Gaut, Mrs. James H. Gaut, or Mrs. E. E. Jones
    - Jones, Helene Marie, 1 photographic print and 1 piece of ephemera (Box 266, Folder 1004)
    - Jones, R. L., Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 266, Folder 1005)
    - Jones, Sarah, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 266, Folder 1006)
    - Jones, W. P., 1 photographic print (Box 266, Folder 1007)
    - Jonsson, Hulda, 1 photographic print (Box 266, Folder 1008)
    - Jonsson, Lisa, 1 photographic print (Box 266, Folder 1009)
    - Jorgensen, Irene Mae (born 1915), 1 color photographic print (Box 267, Folder 1010)
      Also known as Irene Mae Johnson
    - Josefsson, Anna, 1 photographic print (Box 267, Folder 1011)
    - Josefsson, Tilda, 1 photographic print (Box 267, Folder 1012)
    - Judson, A. O., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 267, Folder 1013)
    - Julin, Hilda (1861-1926), 3 photographic prints (Box 267, Folder 1014)
    - Jung, Jo, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 267, Folder 1015)
    - Kahn, Laurie, 3 photographic prints and 1 color photographic prints (Box 267, Folder 1016)
    - Kaida, Tamarra (born 1946), 2 color 35mm slides (Box 267, Folder 1017)
    - Kaplan, Marion, 1 serial (Box 267, Folder 1018)
    - Karlen, De, 1 photographic print (Box 267, Folder 1019)
    - Karlson, Hanna, 2 photographic prints (Box 267, Folder 1020)
    - Karlson, Livan, 1 photographic print (Box 267, Folder 1021)
    - Karlsson, Hanna Elisabeth (born 1876), 1 photographic print (Box 267, Folder 1022)
    - Karlström, Theres, 1 photographic print (Box 267, Folder 1023)
    - Karnow, Catherine, 1 serial (Box 267, Folder 1024)
    - Karp, Kathleen A. (born 1944), 4 color 35mm slides (Box 267, Folder 1025)
    - Käsebier, Gertrude Stanton (1852-1934), 3 photographic prints and 2 serials (Box 267, Folder 1026)
    - Kastman, Ellen, 1 photographic print (Box 267, Folder 1027)
    - Katz, Leslie, 3 color photographic prints (Box 267, Folder 1028)
    - Kaufman, Suzanne, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 267, Folder 1029)
    - Kay, A., 6 color photographic prints (Box 267, Folder 1030)
    - Kaye, Betty, 1 serial (Box 267, Folder 1031)
    - Kegg, Cora E., 8 photographic prints and 1 serial (Box 267, Folder 1032)
    - Kellett, Sarah E. (born circa 1841), 2 photographic prints (Box 267, Folder 1033)
      Also known as Mrs. Thomas A. Kellett
    - Kellner, Tatana, 2 serials (Box 267, Folder 1034)
    - Kelly, Alison, 3 color 35mm slides (Box 267, Folder 1035)
    - Kelly, Joseph, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 267, Folder 1036)
    - Kemp, Josephine A., Mrs., 1 piece of ephemera (Box 267, Folder 1037)
      Also known as Mrs. Edward H. Kemp
    - Kendall, Marie Hartig (1854-1943), 10 photographic prints (Box 267, Folder 1038)
      Also known as Mrs. John C. Kendall
    - Kenneday, Elizabeth Anne (born 1950), 4 color 35mm slides (Box 267, Folder 1039)
    - Kerr, S. Hollis (born 1970), 14 color inkjet prints (Box 267, Folder 1040)
      Also known as Holli Kerr
    - Khazen, Marie el, 1 serial (Box 267, Folder 1041)
    - Kidder, Jacqueline Rose (born 1942), 7 color photographic prints (Box 267, Folder 1042)
    - Kihl, Signe, 1 photographic print (Box 267, Folder 1043)
    - Kihlbaum, Maria, 1 photographic print (Box 267, Folder 1044)
    - Killerby, J. B., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1045)
    - Kimmons, Clara, 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1046)
    - Kindberg, Emma, 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1047)
    - Kindberg, Maria, 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1048)
    - Kindlund, Adéle, 7 photographic prints (Box 268, Folder 1049)
    - King, L. M., Mrs., 3 photographic prints (Box 268, Folder 1050)
    - King, Willie, 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1051)
    - Kirchner, Emma (1830-1909), 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1052)
    - Kirkland, Margaret C., 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1053)
      Also known as Mrs. Frank Kirkland
    - Kittredge, Charmian, 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1054)
    - Kjædebye, Emilie, 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1055)
    - Kleinhammer, Ida M., Miss (born 1874), 5 photographic prints (Box 268, Folder 1056)
    - Klemm, Barbara, 1 serial (Box 268, Folder 1057)
    - Klintberg, Anna, 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1058)
    - Klintö, Anine, 4 photographic prints (Box 268, Folder 1059)
      Also known as Anine Klintö Jensen
    - Klostermann, Corrino Caesarina, Mrs. (1849-1909), 21 photographic prints (Box 268, Folder 1060)
      Also known as Mrs. Frederick Klostermann, Mrs. Homer H. Lambert, or Miss Corrino C. Shaw
    - Knasnionski, Hildegard, 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1061)
    - Knowles, Estelle G. (born circa 1882), 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1062)
    - Knutsson, Eva, 5 photographic prints (Box 268, Folder 1063)
    - Kornstein, Charlotte (born 1939), 1 color 35mm slide (Box 268, Folder 1064)
    - Krane, Lesley (born 1967), 4 color 35mm slides (Box 268, Folder 1065)
    - Kravitz, Susan (born 1943), 1 color 35mm slide (Box 268, Folder 1066)
    - Krei, La Verne J., Mrs., 14 photographic prints (Box 268, Folder 1067)
    - Krone, Charles, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1068)
    - Kruse, Anna, 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1069)
    - Kubes, Amy (born 1965), 43 color photographic prints (Box 269, Folder 1070-1075)
    - Kudinova, Ludmila, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 268, Folder 1076)
    - Kudirka, Nijole, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 268, Folder 1077)
    - Kuylenstjerna, Hilda, 4 photographic prints (Box 268, Folder 1078)
    - Kvarnström, Systrarna, 5 photographic prints (Box 268, Folder 1079)
    - La Fleur, D., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 268, Folder 1080)
    - La Nina, 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1081)
    - LaBolle, June, 1 color photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1082)
      Also known as Mrs. Victor LaBolle
    - Lacey, E. G., Mrs., 6 photographic prints (Box 268, Folder 1083)
    - Ladd, Ellen Elizabeth (1859-1922), 56 photographic prints and 1 book (Box 270, Folder 1084-1086)
      Also known as Nellie E. Ladd
    - Ladd, Sarah Hall (1857-1927), 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1087)
      Also known as Mrs. Charles Eliott Ladd
    - LaDuke, Betty (born 1933), 10 photographic prints and 1 color photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1088)
    - Lagergren, Ebba, 3 photographic prints (Box 268, Folder 1089)
    - Lagerstam, Anna Elin (1877-1966), 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1090)
      Also known as Ella Lagerstam
    - Lajoie, V., Madame, 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1091)
    - Lake, Jennie S., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 268, Folder 1092)
    - Lamaina, Suzun Lucia, 3 color 35mm slides (Box 268, Folder 1093)
    - Landgrebe, Seraphina, 1 color photographic print (Box 271, Folder 1094)
    - Land-Weber, Ellen (born 1943), 1 photographic print, 1 color inkjet print, and 5 serials (Box 271, Folder 1095)
      Also known as Ellen Epstein
    - Lange, Dorothea (1895-1965), 3 photographic prints and 4 serials (Box 271, Folder 1096)
    - Langford, Olive (born 1868), 2 photographic prints (Box 271, Folder 1097)
    - Langkjær, Emilie, 1 photographic print (Box 271, Folder 1098)
    - Lansdale, Margaret, 2 color photographic prints (Box 271, Folder 1099)
    - LaPerle, Adel, 2 photographic prints (Box 271, Folder 1100)
    - Larimer, Sarah Luse (born 1836), 3 photographic prints (Box 271, Folder 1101)
    - Larrabee, Constance Stuart (1914-2000), 3 photographic prints (Box 271, Folder 1102)
    - Larsen, Augusta, 1 photographic print (Box 271, Folder 1103)
    - Larson, Betty, 3 photographic prints (Box 271, Folder 1104)
    - Larson, Marie, 1 photographic print (Box 271, Folder 1105)
    - Larson, Selma, Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 271, Folder 1106)
    - Larsson, Gerda, 1 photographic print (Box 271, Folder 1107)
    - Larsson, Maria, 2 photographic prints (Box 271, Folder 1108)
    - Lasinsky, Laura (1844-1919), 2 photographic prints (Box 271, Folder 1109)
    - Lasley, Margaret Rose (1874-1950), 13 photographic prints and 2 color photographic prints (Box 271, Folder 1110)
    - Lassiter, Alice E., Mrs. (born circa 1861), 1 photographic print (Box 271, Folder 1111)
    - Latourette, Hattie, Mrs., 1 tintype (Box 271, Folder 1112)
      Also known as Mrs. Hattie Larourrette
    - Lauffer, Martin P., Mrs., 26 photographic prints and 1 album (86 photographic prints) (Box 272, Folder 1113-1131)
    - Lauffer, Sophie L. (1876-1970), 3 photographic prints and 1 serial (Box 271, Folder 1132)
    - Laurberg, Julie Rasmine Marie, Miss (1856-1925), 6 photographic prints (Box 271, Folder 1133)
    - Lavenson, Alma R. (1897-1989), 2 photographic prints (Box 271, Folder 1134)
      Also known as Alma R. Lavenson Wahrhaftig
    - Lavoie, Peg, 3 color photographic prints (Box 271, Folder 1135)
    - Lawhun, S. Marion, Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 271, Folder 1136)
    - Lawrence, Mildred Gregg Griffin, Mrs. (born 1917), 1 color photographic print (Box 271, Folder 1137)
    - Lawton, A. J., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 271, Folder 1138)
    - Le Duc, Maggie, 1 color photographic print and 22 color inkjet prints (Box 271, Folder 1139)
    - Le Prat, Thérèse (1895-1966), 2 photographic prints (Box 271, Folder 1140)
      Also known as Therese Cahen
    - Leach, Jennie, Miss (born 1872), 1 photographic print (Box 271, Folder 1141)
    - Lee, Cecilia Hae-Jin, 2 color 35mm slides (Box 271, Folder 1142)
    - Leeson, Adelaide Hanscom (1876-1932), 5 photographic prints, 1 color photographic print, and 1 dismantled book (Box 273, Folder 1143-1145)
      Also known as Adelaide Hanscom
    - Lefrén, Louise, 7 photographic prints (Box 271, Folder 1146)
    - LeGary, Patti (born 1943), 4 photographic prints (Box 271, Folder 1147)
    - Lehmann, E., Frau, 1 photographic print (Box 271, Folder 1148)
    - Leibovitz, Annie (born 1949), 2 photographic prints (Box 271, Folder 1149)
    - Leigh, M. E., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 271, Folder 1150)
    - Leigh, Wendy, 1 color ink jet print and 1 color 35mm slide (Box 271, Folder 1151)
    - Lekander, Helfrid, 1 photographic print (Box 271, Folder 1152)
    - Léon, Veuve, 1 photographic print (Box 274, Folder 1153)
    - Leonard, Joanne (born 1940), 6 photographic prints and 3 serials (Box 274, Folder 1154)
    - Levi, Clara, Mrs. (born circa 1838), 2 photographic prints (Box 274, Folder 1155)
      Also known as Mrs. C. H. Levi or Mrs. Henry Levi
    - Levine, Suzanne, 2 serials (Box 274, Folder 1156)
    - Levy, Mary Clara, Miss (1866-1948), 4 photographic prints (Box 274, Folder 1157)
      Also known as Miss Mary Clara Godeus or Mrs. Kossuth Charles Levy
    - Lewallen, Eva, Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 274, Folder 1158)
    - Lewis, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 274, Folder 1159)
      Also known as Lewis and Wife
    - Lewis, Bonnie, 1 photographic print (Box 274, Folder 1160)
    - Lewis, J. B., Mrs., 6 photographic prints (Box 274, Folder 1161)
    - Lewis, M. Emma, Mrs., 1 photographic print, hand-colored (Box 274, Folder 1162)
    - Lewis, M. L., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 274, Folder 1163)
    - Ley, Mary M., 1 photographic print (Box 274, Folder 1164)
      Also known as Mrs. Thomas Allen Ley
    - Liang, Genevieve, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 274, Folder 1165)
    - Libby, Minnie F., Miss, 23 photographic prints and 1 piece of ephemera (Box 274, Folder 1166)
    - Liljenberg, Alli, 1 photographic print (Box 274, Folder 1167)
      Also known as Alli Liljeberg
    - Lindberg, Adèle, 1 photographic print (Box 274, Folder 1168)
    - Lindgren, Berta, 1 photographic print (Box 274, Folder 1169)
    - Lindgren, Ester, 1 photographic print (Box 274, Folder 1170)
    - Lindholm, Siri, 1 photographic print (Box 274, Folder 1171)
    - Lindquist, Anny, Miss, 17 photographic prints (Box 274, Folder 1172)
    - Lindsay, J. F., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 274, Folder 1173)
    - Lindståhl, Anna, 1 photographic print (Box 274, Folder 1174)
    - Lindstedt, Ebba, 1 photographic print (Box 274, Folder 1175)
    - Lindström, Alexia, 2 photographic prints (Box 274, Folder 1176)
    - Lockhart, Maggie G., Miss, 1 stereograph (Box 274, Folder 1177)
    - Lockwood, Eunice N., Mrs. (born circa 1841), 29 photographic prints and 1 tintype (Box 274, Folder 1178)
      Also known as Mrs. W. N. Lockwood
    - Lockwood, M. L., Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 274, Folder 1179)
    - Loehr, Pearl Grace (born circa 1880), 2 photographic prints and 1 serial (Box 274, Folder 1180)
    - Logemann, Clara A., Miss, 4 photographic prints (Box 274, Folder 1181)
      Also known as Logemann Sisters, Logemann & Strye, or Mrs. Clara E. Logemann Strye
    - London, Elsye (born circa 1894), 1 color photographic print (Box 274, Folder 1182)
    - London, Laura S., 2 color 35mm slides (Box 274, Folder 1183)
    - Long, Cora W., Mrs., 8 photographic prints (Box 274, Folder 1184)
      Also known as Mrs. C. B. Long or Mrs. C. C. Long
    - Longo, Colleen, 4 photographic prints and 2 color photographic prints (Box 274, Folder 1185)
    - Lorillard, Eva Paxton, Mrs. (born 1860), 6 photographic prints (Box 274, Folder 1186)
    - Lotz, Matilda (born 1858), 3 photographic prints (Box 275, Folder 1187)
    - Lowengrim, Louisa, Miss (born circa 1861), 1 photographic print (Box 275, Folder 1188)
    - Löwenson, Amalia, 3 photographic prints (Box 275, Folder 1189)
    - Lowry, Sandra Hoffman, 1 color photographic print (Box 275, Folder 1190)
    - Lucore, Emma, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 275, Folder 1191)
    - Lund, Johanna (1857-1933), 5 photographic prints (Box 275, Folder 1192)
    - Lund, Karen, 2 photographic prints (Box 275, Folder 1193)
    - Lund, Kirstine (1852-1948), 2 photographic prints (Box 275, Folder 1194)
    - Lundbäck, Maria, 16 photographic prints (Box 275, Folder 1195)
    - Lundbeck, Calla, 1 photographic print (Box 275, Folder 1196)
    - Lundborg, Hanna, 10 photographic prints (Box 275, Folder 1197)
    - Lunder, Ruth, 1 photographic print (Box 275, Folder 1198)
    - Lundevall, Lina, 1 photographic print (Box 275, Folder 1199)
    - Lundmark, Mia, 1 photographic print (Box 275, Folder 1200)
    - Lundquist, Jean, 1 photographic print (Box 275, Folder 1201)
    - Lundquist, Maria, 2 photographic prints (Box 275, Folder 1202)
    - Luskačová, Markéta (born 1944), 2 serials (Box 275, Folder 1203)
    - Lutgen, L., Mrs., 1 postcard (Box 275, Folder 1204)
    - Lyon, D. D., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 275, Folder 1205)
    - MacDougall, Mardell (born circa 1897), 1 photographic print (Box 275, Folder 1206)
    - MacIntyre, Mary, 7 photographic prints (Box 275, Folder 1207)
    - MacKay, Elizabeth (born 1958), 3 photographic prints (Box 275, Folder 1208)
    - MacLeod, Kate, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 275, Folder 1209)
    - Macris-Gillespie, Myrto, 6 color photographic prints (Box 275, Folder 1210)
    - Madden, Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 275, Folder 1211)
      Also known as Miss M. Madden or Misses Madden and Robinson
    - Madden, M. J., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 275, Folder 1212)
    - Madden, Mary, Mrs., 6 photographic prints (Box 275, Folder 1213)
    - Maeder, Cheryl, 2 color 35mm slides (Box 275, Folder 1214)
    - Magee, Gladys, 1 photographic print (Box 275, Folder 1215)
    - Magnusson, Anna, 2 photographic prints (Box 275, Folder 1216)
    - Major, V. E., Mrs., 2 serials (Box 275, Folder 1217)
    - Malek, Diane, 1 photographic print (Box 275, Folder 1218)
    - Mann, Margery (1919-1977), 1 photographic print (Box 275, Folder 1219)
      Also known as Margery Mann Vasey
    - Mann, May Baker, Mrs., 4 photographic prints (Box 275, Folder 1220)
    - Manning, F. M., and Lady, 1 tintype (Box 275, Folder 1221)
    - Mansfield, Charlotte D. (born 1915), 163 photographic prints (Box 276, Folder 1222-1229)
    - Mariolle, Elaine, 1 serial (Box 275, Folder 1230)
    - Mariosa, Olga, 2 color 35mm slides (Box 275, Folder 1231)
    - Mark, Mary Ellen (born 1940), 1 photographic print (Box 275, Folder 1232)
    - Marsh, Ruby L., Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 275, Folder 1233)
    - Marshall, Karen, 1 serial (Box 275, Folder 1234)
    - Marsted, Marcia Reid, 10 color 35mm slides (Box 275, Folder 1235)
    - Mårtenson, Augusta, 1 photographic print (Box 277, Folder 1236)
    - Martin, Bessie, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 277, Folder 1237)
    - Martin, Mary E., Miss, 1 serial (Box 277, Folder 1238)
    - Martin, Minnie Marie Martha (1887-1981), 10 color inkjet prints (Box 277, Folder 1239)
      Also known as Minnie Marie Martha Paul
    - Martin, Nancy A. (born 1948), 4 color 35mm slides (Box 277, Folder 1240)
    - Martin, Nancy L. (born 1950), 9 color 35mm slides (Box 277, Folder 1241)
    - Mary, 1 photographic print (Box 277, Folder 1242)
    - Mason, Jean, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 277, Folder 1243)
    - Mason, P. G., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 277, Folder 1244)
    - Mast, Mary A., 2 photographic prints (Box 277, Folder 1245)
      Also known as Mrs. Seth P. Mast
    - Masters, E. A., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 277, Folder 1246)
    - Mather, Margrethe (1885-1952), 1 photographic print (Box 277, Folder 1247)
    - Matson, Frances L., Miss, 7 photographic prints (Box 277, Folder 1248)